Huh?
Where are we?
We were at the Emperor's Tower.
Saneatsu, look!
Saaya!
Welcome back Saneatsu and Saaya!
We don't have much time.
My Presentation Right will give you
directions to follow, for real!
There should be monitors around you.
I'll show you what's been happening and where to head.
You can catch up with us as you read them!
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
It was an insane plan.
It didn't matter how many
of us died, foe or ally.
The only thing that mattered was stalling,
so that the Emperor, Queen,
and Teppei stayed put.
Yagihashi, you were always
planning for the bigger picture,
unlike the rest of us.
As for me, I'll put an end to this.
For good!
Raion, what happened to Kou and Iruga?
Don't panic when you hear this.
They were both killed.
But we were able to annihilate the enemy.
The best we could do was seclude
Yagihashi in a divided space.
So we won by a narrow margin.
I'm glad you're okay though, Raion.
I'm only the messenger, so I don't
understand what this means but,
"I leave the Mother Light to Lady Kisaragi.
It should be under your full command."
That was the message he left for you.
I see.
There's no one waiting
at the church to bless us. So...
Let's resurrect Teppei right here.
It's our only option given the circumstance.
Once we revive Teppei and the
Obedience Right is in our hands,
the world will be under our command.
Before that, I want to talk with Haruto.
You have a lot of catching up to do
as siblings once Teppei's alive.
I figured we should talk before that.
I understand.
What's this about?
I have something important to tell you.
They need us for something.
Raion has the ultimate defense against the Emperor, so he'll be fine no matter what.
So I need you to focus on just one thing.
Use "Ryuta's last gift"!
Ryuta's last gift...
Haruto, I want you to retract
your negotiation with me.
What?
Wh-What do you mean retract it?!
Don't take it the wrong way.
As long as the Negotiation Right
requires me to stay loyal to you,
I can't prove that my friendship
isn't out of obligation.
Okay. I believe in you, Raion.
Everything we've been through
has gotta be real...
so I retract my negotiation agreement!
One more thing, Haruto.
Huh?
You said you want it to be real.
So let's make a new agreement.
I'll tell you how I truly feel about you.
In return, you'll have to hear me out.
It scares me, but I want to
know how you really feel,
so I'll do it!
You good with me finalizing that?
Yeah.
Negotiation complete.
This isn't related to our plans.
It's not even necessary.
But that's okay with me.
This is my truth that replaces
the "love" command.
I lost my closest relative in Tasuketsu.
I'll be honest: I hated you.
But as we spent time together, I realized...
you were just a normal kid too.
I started seeing you as Haruto,
not the Emperor.
Someone who wanted to be friends with me,
and who laughed like a normal kid.
You may have done something
terrible as the Emperor.
But I've decided that no matter
what anyone tells me,
no matter how contradictory it may seem,
I won't lie to myself anymore.
Even if you have an evil side
that betrayed people,
I know there's someone genuine behind that.
I'll believe in the real you!
I promise!
No matter what happens from now on,
I swear I'll come save you!
Raion!
I swear I'll believe in you!
I won't do bad stuff anymore!
I was wrong to do all of that!
Raion, it's just as I thought.
You don't want to be crying
when we revive Teppei, do you?
I'm not crying! I'm fine!
You ready?
Production Attribute.
Prime Right of Resurrection!
You'll be back in our arms at last, Teppei.
Huh? Where am I?
Big bro!
Is that voice... Haruto?
We've missed you, Teppei.
Is that Big Sis?
Is it really you guys?
How? And where are we?
We're in Tokyo.
Iruga helped us find you.
Ren did?! Is he here right now?!
No, he's not. Let me explain everything.
An organization called the
"Rights Specimen Laboratory Camp"
announced a large-scale terrorist attack
and it's caused a panic.
The Camp!
So that's what's going on...
The area you were in was exposed to it.
Iruga sensed you were both in danger
and escaped with you.
He was a frequent visitor
at my friend's church.
We were very lucky to have met.
A large-scale terrorist attack?
I don't remember any news like that
on the radio before I fell asleep.
You were asleep for three days.
Three days?!
Iruga told us everything about the Camp.
We're working together right now
to save the subjects.
Teppei, give me your Obedience Right.
What? The Obedience Right?
The terrorist attack was just a diversion.
There's been incidents of researchers
stealing Rights from subjects
while they're asleep.
You're in danger with the
Obedience Right in your hands.
We're all safer with it in
an outsider's hands.
Which is why I want you to give it to me.
Sis, so Ren's out there
saving people right now?
Yes.
Thank goodness.
He's finally come around.
I understand, then let me—
Hey, mind if I introduce myself?
Wait, there's someone else here?
It's my best friend, Big Bro.
Nice to meet you, I'm Raion Ouno.
I see Haruto is in good hands. Thank you.
Sorry, I didn't mean to ruin the moment.
I just couldn't handle being out of the loop!
Makes sense, my bad.
Hopefully that bought us a bit more time.
Is this how Ryuta found us?
If Gobo's message is true...
The same Emperor that Ryuta
couldn't find back then
must be who I'm looking at right now.
Remember what you said at the park?
Huh?
You taught me how to take a picture.
It's all about focusing on or
framing around the main shot.
I finally get what you meant by that.
It's too early for friendly chit-chat.
We're not out of the woods until
we transfer the Obedience Right.
You're right, Sis. Let's do that first.
Now!
I declare parenthood!
I order the Obedience Right...
to transfer itself to my big sister.
It's done! Our suffering has been rewarded!
That should have transferred
the Obedience Right to you.
Thank you, Teppei.
Now we can crush the Camp's plans.
Sis, why don't you try
using it just to be safe?
You're right.
I'll cure your eyesight
with the Obedience Right.
Do you mind?
I guess it's better to be safe. Okay.
I order Teppei's eyes to be cured!
So? Did it work?
Can you see me?!
No, I can't. I'm still blind.
It failed?!
B-But how?
Checkmate!
All right, Saneatsu Narita.
All of our hope has led to this moment.
Put an end to this!
I exercise my Parental Authority
against Teppei Yoshii.
I'll now exercise the
Obedience Right on his behalf!
I order—
Tasuketsu: Fate of the Majority
Mornin', Saneatsu!
What's up? You're always
so energetic, Kazuhiko.
Man, you must really hate informatics!
Informatics? You mean computer
class. I'm just so bad at it.
When it comes to computers,
you're "Sorry-atsu"!
Shaddup!
Is Ryuta here yet?
He's prolly late again!
Enough talking, guys. Turn your PCs on.
Yeah, yeah.
Mornin'.
You're late, Ryuta!
Not that you're missing anything.
All right then. Sensei, we gotta leave early!
All right. Then today's class
will be study hall.
What?!
Mm-help!
It's not good to skip school!
You're skipping too!
You two, quiet down!
Okay.
I-I wasn't using my
Compliance Right that time.
I know, Senpai.
In the end, I used my Parental Authority
to use the Obedience Right.
And I turned back time to today.
I've heard that the Obedience Right
is the strongest Right.
But why turn back time to today?
I still have a prosthetic right eye,
not to mention the Visualization Right.
Why not wipe away the Camp's entire existence?
The command needed to be short and concise.
Retain the memories
of everyone involved with us.
Retain the memories of everyone involved with us.
Rights shall stay with their owners
as of June 14.
Rights shall stay with their owners as of June 14.
And turn back time to June 5.
If the Camp never existed,
I wouldn't have met ya guys.
The test run didn't occur.
Our plan is about 80% complete.
Now we just have two more things to do!
Okay, let's pick up the pace!
You know, I don't think
this place needs guards.
Probably not. I can't think of
anyone who'd come here.
Huh?
Stop! Who the hell are you?!
How did you get here?!
With that.
Prime Right of Immobilization.
Perfect. You're up next!
Touya Mutsuki!
Multiply gravity by 100 million!
Who would've thought
you'd be so willing to help?
I gotta thank you, Queen!
Returning to this day
helped me come to my senses.
Although, I'm still upset you tricked us.
But I understand where you're coming from.
I'm in full agreement. Let's do it.
We'll resurrect you later, so go all out!
Got it.
Are you sure we can trust him, Kisaragi-san?
My lies were always for my own sake.
However, I can't help but feel as though
Raion lies from a place
of goodwill and kindness.
So, I'd like to trust him.
It's a monster!
They're using Rights!
Must be a revenge attack by escapees!
Hurry and inform the others!
Huh?! I can't move!
I stopped you with space division!
Then I'll point them the right way.
What's going on?!
Mind if you lead the way?
Sudo!
Good work.
It's the Camp's transceiver. Take it!
I'll mass-produce it using my Right.
Yagihashi, spread them across
the Camp with your Induction Right!
So Raion and the others can use them, right?
Large-scale damages seen
across the entire facility!
Cause unknown!
Impossible. How could it suddenly...
Director Kirishima! State of emergency!
We're under attack
by a group of Rights owners!
They've mastered the Rights
far beyond our level!
They're trampling all through our facility!
We can't stop them!
Th-There's no way! Impossible!
There we go! For real!
All right then, let's finish this up!
I've sent the map to you guys!
Attack the Camp... Is that
the first of our remaining tasks?
No, we're just warming up.
We really did a number on them.
All clear here!
We'll lead the test subjects!
Mm-what?!
It's the facility map!
Someone must have found it
and sent it to Gobo.
Perfect, we've done enough.
Let's move out.
Control Room
Bring out our best experiment!
He'll take care of them!
In the VIP Room on the fifth floor. Hurry!
Ye-Yes sir!
You heard him. See ya!
Pretty much as I figured.
Ready, Knight?
Sure am!
Go big brother!
Destruction Right!
As promised, I'm here to save you, Haruto.
Yeah. I knew you'd come, Raion.
There was no test run,
which meant no Tasuketsu.
It was all so you wouldn't become the Emperor.
For us to free you from
the shackles of the Emperor,
this was our only way.
But still, that meant
I had to lie to you... a lot.
I'm sorry, Haruto.
Like you said, Raion.
No matter how much I betrayed people,
you'd believe in the real me.
Same goes for me.
No matter how much you lie,
I believe in the real you!
Yeah.
Big Bro! Big Sis!
That's how reunions ought to be.
Let's get the most important
part out of the way.
Are you Kou Kirishima?
I am. Are you Saneatsu Narita?
I assume you understand the plan by now.
Of course.
This will end things once and for all.
From fighting to protect others,
to fighting to save others.
It's all thanks to you.
Thank you, Raion Ouno.
The only person I saved is Haruto.
You're the one who saved
the world, Saneatsu Narita.
Now for the last step!
Once again, I declare parenthood
to Teppei Yoshii.
I order all victims related
to this Camp be resurrected.
I order all victims related to this Camp be resurrected.
All sacrifices given in turn
for Rights shall be reversed,
I order for victims related to this Camp be resurrected.
All sacrifices given in turn for Rights shall be reversed,
unless otherwise intended by the owner.
unless otherwise intended
by the owner.
The Mother Light shall lose its powers
and shatter into pieces.
And finally, all Rights shall be returned
to the world of consciousness!
It's over.
Cool!
Wha!
Haruto, what's up with your eyes?!
Lame!
Don't laugh! These are
my natural eyes, you idiot!
Phew.
Sis, Haruto, I heard about everything you did.
Brace yourselves for a long
lecture about all this!
Okay...
Take it easy on them. After all,
the past has been totally erased!
Welcome back, Teppei-chan.
I'm home, Ren.
Oh, looks like the victims are back.
Omi? Is that Omi?!
Dad! Mom!
Erased or not, the ones who know
will remember what happened.
Narita, you sure made the right call.
Now, let's go back. To our normal lives!
And the future that
was waiting for us all along!
Not long after, the Camp's
Director Junichi Kirishima was
arrested as the main culprit
of a large-scale kidnapping.
He and the rest of the researchers
were sent to prison.
And so, without even a trace of the Rights,
the world returned back to normal.
Still, as long as we're connected,
it'll remain a fragment of the truth,
leaving behind a few mysteries
hidden in our memories.
'Sup!
Heading home alone?
Let's hit the arcade!
Don't get me mixed up in this!
Now's our chance!
As long as we're connected,
it'll remain a fragment of the truth.
Which might not be all that bad.
Towards the Light
Not bad at all.
Thank you!